(Sheldon:)Really?
(Sheldon:)Why?
(Leonard:)Because you're impossible
to work with.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)And is that open
for discussion?
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Oh. Good morning, shoemaker.
(Sheldon:)I think you'll be pleased
(Sheldon:)with what the elves were up to
last night.
(Leonard:)But I fired you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I know. I'm now
an independent contractor.
(Leonard:)No, you are
now nothing.
(Leonard:)You have no connection
to this project whatsoever.
(Sheldon:)But I made it better.
(Leonard:)I don't want it better.
I want it my way.
(Sheldon:)Well, that speaks volumes,
doesn't it?
(Sheldon:)All right, I suppose
I'll go put on my bus pants.
(Leonard:)What the hell are bus pants?
(Sheldon:)They are pants one wears
over one's regular pants
(Sheldon:)when one sits on bus seats
(Sheldon:)that other people
have previously sat on.